newshare.com 2018-01-12

# CircLabs Inc. privacy policy

## Privacy Policy Statement

### What products and services are covered in this privacy policy?

This privacy policy applies to the present circlabs.com website and to the Newshare/Circulate service. 

### What information do we collect?

We and our affiliate, Taxonometrics Inc., collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address or zip code. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website and services**  
(we continually strive to improve our web and mobile offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer-service requests and support needs)
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing and/or to sign up to use the Newshare/Circulate prototype service, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or service, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

### Do we use "cookies"?

We or our affiliate, Taxonometrics Inc., may use standard Internet protocols to store a temporary or persistent file ("cookie") on your computer or other device. This information is used in subsequent sessions ("visits") to associate you with a particular set of stored news preferences. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties, other than to our technology partner, Taxonometrics Inc., your personally identifiable information or news profile information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as we believe those parties keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is required by law, such as in order to enforce our site policies, or protect ours' or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Advertising

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

### Uses not otherwise disclosed

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

### Access to your profile

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the address below. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the same address. 

### Your Consent

By using our web servers, including Newshare/CircLabs, you consent to our [website and service privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/). 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

### Contacting Us

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at address below. The Direct Market Association's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm. 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

75 Water St  
Williamstown, MA 01267  
United States  
+1-617-458-8001
